## **ABOUT ME**

My name is Jarosław Janas and I'm a Front-End Developer. I started my work with code in 2020. I really enjoy it and I want to be a better Web-Developer every day. My specialization is creating websites and applications in JavaScript language.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - NOW



Hotel Receptionist - Aparthotel Miodowa

Cracow

checking reservations, service for hotel guests, taking care of the positive image of the hotel

2018 - 2018



Soldier of Polish Army – 22<sup>nd</sup> Mountain Infantry Battalion,

Kłodzko

military service for the country, improvement in: strategy, military leadership, shooting, rescue and defense against weapons of mass destruction

2017 - 2018



**Hostel Menager – Heynow Hostel** 

Cracow

hostel administrations, marketing, recruitment and management of new employees, operating reservation systems, taking care of the positive image of the hostel

# **EDUCATION**

2020 - NOW



Front-End Developer – Courses on the UDEMY e-learning platform

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT

2017 - 2019



Master Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

education for security and crisis management

2014 - 2017



Bachelor Degree – Pedagogical University of Cracow

national security



# **Jarosław Janas**

### **CONTACT**



+48 798 194 305



jarekjanas95@gmail.com



https://jarek-portfolio.netlify.app



Cracow 31-222, Poland

### **SKILLS**

#### **Professional:**



HTML



CSS



**JAVASCRIPT** 



**REACT** 

#### **Personal:**

- CREATIVITY
- SELF-MOTIVATION
- TEAM WORK
- SCRUPULOUSNESS

#### Languages:

- POLISH
- ENGLISH